Contact

E-10, Islamabad 923339700813 (Mobile) wasifarslan81@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/muhammadwasif-arslan-51833020a (LinkedIn) www.upwork.com/freelancers/ ~01e052a544aebeb502 (Company)

Top Skills

Microsoft Office Adobe Photoshop HTML

Muhammad Wasif Arslan

DevOps Engineer | Data Scientist

Islāmābād

Summary

Have You Been Looking For An Awesome Expert MERN Stack Developer?

I have been working with Javascript for 3 years, I work quickly with high stamina for doing big projects on a short time scale. Let's create something cool together!

My expertise includes:

- Front-end responsive web application using HTML, CSS, Javascript (PWA), j Bootstrap, React and Redux
- MongoDB
- REST APIs using Express
- NodeJS
- Docker
- Kubernetes
- Mobile apps using React Native framework

Services:

- # React.js
- # Redux
- # Ant Design
- # Material UI
- # animate.css
- # Styled-component
- # React Native
- # React Native elements
- # Bootstrap
- # Axios
- # fetch
- # Ajax.

Database:

- # MongoDB
- # MySQL

Cloud computing platforms:

Amazon Web Services

Firebase

Our Values:

100% Client Satisfaction

Experience

Upwork

Data Scientist

March 2018 - Present (3 years 5 months)

Fiverr

3 years 7 months

DevOps Engineer

March 2018 - Present (3 years 5 months)

DevOps Engineer

February 2018 - Present (3 years 6 months)

Architect

January 2018 - March 2018 (3 months)

Education

National University of Sciences and Technology (NUST)

Bachelor of Science - BS, Information Technology · (February 2018 - February 2022)